{"categories":[],"description":" Based on the clues, name these characters from fairy tales and nursery rhymes. ","difficulty":-1,"questions":[{"answer":"Cinderella","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Owner of a glass slipper"},{"answer":"Hansel","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Gretel's brother"},{"answer":"Snow White","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"She eats a poisoned apple, but is revived by a prince's kiss"},{"answer":"Humpty Dumpty","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Egg who \"had a great fall\""},{"answer":"Rapunzel","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Her hair becomes a prince's ladder"},{"answer":"Jack","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Traded a cow for magic beans"},{"answer":"Sleeping Beauty","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Princess who sleeps for a hundred years"},{"answer":"Big Bad Wolf","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Little Red Riding Hood's enemy"},{"answer":"Fairy Godmother","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Turns a pumpkin into a carriage, among other exploits"},{"answer":"Frog Prince","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Amphibian who transforms when kissed"},{"answer":"Three Little Pigs","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Two of their three houses are blown down"},{"answer":"Ugly Duckling","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Duck that is actually a swan"},{"answer":"Little Mermaid","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Loses her flippers for a prince's love"},{"answer":"Rumpelstiltskin","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Strangely-named imp who can spin straw into gold"},{"answer":"Pied Piper","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Leads the rats and town children away"},{"answer":"Gingerbread Man","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Cookie comes to life and proves difficult to catch"},{"answer":"Prince Charming","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Stock character who is the object of female fantasies"},{"answer":"Puss in Boots","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Cunning cat who becomes a French bigwig"},{"answer":"Rip Van Winkle","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"American man who falls asleep for twenty years"},{"answer":"Golden Goose","category":"Fairy Tale Characters","question":"Sticky waterfowl owned by Simpleton"}],"title":"Fairy Tale Characters"}